A Finding Aid to the Exhibition Records of the Contemporary Study Wing of the Finch College Museum of Art, 1943-1975, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Exhibition Files, 1943-1975; Series 4; Archival Resource Key; 14.9 Linear feet Boxes 6-22, OV 24-25, FC 26
  - "Projected Art" (1966-1967), Archival Resource Key (Box 17)
    - Artist Files, Archival Resource Key (Box 17)
      - Richard Geredasy and Tom McDonough, 1967-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 46)
      - Mordi Gerstein, 1967-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 47)
      - Leonard Glasser, 1967-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 48)
      - Red Grooms, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 49)
      - Hilary Harris, 1967-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 50)
      - Ian Hugo, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 51)
      - George Kuchar, 1967-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 52)
      - Dan McLaughlin, 1967-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 53)
      - Jonas Mekas, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 54)
      - Fred Mogubgub, 1967-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 55)
      - Robert Nelson, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 56)
      - Hans Richter, 1967-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 57)
      - Stan Vanderbeek, 1966-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 58)
        Includes a floor plan for a proposed, untitled, multi-channel installation work
      - Andy Warhol, 1967-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 59)
      - Jud Yalkut, 1967-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 60)
    - Bills, Receipts, and Price List, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 61)
    - Catalog Text, circa 1966-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 62)
    - Clippings, 1966-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 63)
    - Correspondence, 1966-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 64)
    - Correspondence, 1966-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 65)
    - Correspondence, 1966-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 66)
    - Correspondence, 1966-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 67)
    - Film Evaluations, circa 1966-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 68)
    - Film Research, circa 1966-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 69)
    - Film Research, circa 1966-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 70)
    - Film Research, circa 1966-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 71)
    - Film Research, circa 1966-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 72)
    - "Girl Behind the Lens", undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 73)
      Motion picture film stored separately in film can numbered FC 26
    - Girl Behind the Lens, Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel 16mm (Item FC 26)
  - "Projected Art" (1966-1967), Archival Resource Key (Box 18)
    - Lists of Films and Filmmakers, circa 1966-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Lists of Films and Filmmakers, circa 1966-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - New York State Council on the Arts, 1966-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - New York State Council on the Arts, 1966-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Photographs of Film Stills, circa 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Program Requests, 1966-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - "Projected Art: Artists at Work" (1971), Archival Resource Key (Box 18)
    - Artist Biographies, circa 1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Artist Biography Research, circa 1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 8)
      Oversized photocopied clippings housed in OV 25.
    - Artist Biography Research, circa 1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Artist Biography Research, circa 1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Artist Biography Research, circa 1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Artist Biography Research, circa 1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Artist Biography Research, circa 1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Clippings, 1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 14)
      Oversized clippings housed in OV 25.
    - Correspondence, 1970-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, 1970-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, 1970-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, 1970-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Corrrespondence, 1970-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, 1970-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Film Procurement, 1969-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Film Procurement, 1969-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Film Procurement, 1969-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Interview with Doris Chase, circa 1970; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound tape reel (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Lists and Installation Instructions, circa 1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - New York State Council on the Arts Contracts, 1970-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Notes and Research, 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Photographs, 1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Photographs, 1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Press Releases and Announcement, 1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Video Recordings, Archival Resource Key (Box 18)
      - Lynda Benglis, Kansas State Union Pieces, 1971; Archival Resource Key; 1 Videoreels (1/2 inch) (Box 18, Folder 31, Item 1)
      - Michael Singer Building His Sculpture, "Balance III", 1971; Archival Resource Key; 1 Videoreels (1/2 inch) (Box 18, Folder 31, Item 2)
      - Sam Wiener, circa 1971; Archival Resource Key; 1 Videoreels (1/2 inch) (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - "René Bouché: Portraits of Figures in the Arts" (1967), Archival Resource Key (Box 18)
    - Bills and Receipts, 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Catalog, Writings and Research, 1957-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Correspondence, 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - Correspondence, 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - Homages to René Bouché, 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 37)
      Oversized handwritten statement signed "Matta" in box 22, folder 6.
    - Lists, circa 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - Loan Agreements, 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - Loan Agreements, 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - Photographs of Artwork, circa 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - Photographs of Artwork, circa 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 42)
    - Photographs of Installation Views and Opening, 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 43)
    - Press Release, Announcement, and Clippings, 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 44)
      Oversized clippings in box 22, folder 6.
  - "Robert Monroe: Essence of Form" (1967), Archival Resource Key (Box 18)
    - Announcement and Clippings, 1966-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 45)
    - Catalog Drafts, Final Catalog, and Notes, circa 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 46)
    - Letter and Loan Form, 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 47)
    - Photographs of Artwork, circa 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 48)
    - Photographs of Installation, 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 49)
  - "Salvation Army Art Collection" (1968), circa 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 50)
  - "Schemata 7" (1967), Archival Resource Key (Box 18)
    - Announcement, Press Release, and Clippings, 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 51)
      Oversized pamphlet in box 22, folder 6.
    - Artist Résumés, circa 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 52)
    - Catalog and Catalog Drafts, 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 53)
    - Correspondence and Notes, circa 1966-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 54)
    - Interview Transcripts, 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 55)
    - Interview Transcripts, 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 56)
  - "Schemata 7" (1967), Archival Resource Key (Box 19)
    - Interviews, Archival Resource Key (Box 19)
      - Will Insley, circa 1967; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound tape reel (Box 19, Folder 1, Item 1)
      - Michael Kirby, circa 1967; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound tape reel (Box 19, Folder 1, Item 2)
      - Les Levine, circa 1967; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound tape reel (Box 19, Folder 2, Item 1)
      - Ursula Meyer, circa 1967; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound tape reel (Box 19, Folder 2, Item 2)
      - Brian O'Doherty, circa 1967; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound tape reel (Box 19, Folder 3, Item 1)
      - Charles Ross, circa 1967; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound tape reel (Box 19, Folder 3, Item 2)
      - Tony Smith, circa 1967; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound tape reel (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Loan Forms, 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Photographs for Catalog, circa 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Photographs of Artists and Artwork, circa 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Photographs of Artists and Artwork, circa 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Schematic Drawings or Michael Kirby Installation, 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - "Selections from the Permanent Collection" (1971), Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - "Selections from the Permanent Collection" (1974), Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - "Seven Swedish Painters" (1965), Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - "Sonia Sekula" (1972), Archival Resource Key (Box 19)
    - Catalog, Press Release, Announcement, and Clipping, 1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence and Receipts, 1971-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence and Receipts, 1971-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence and Receipts, 1971-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Customs, 1971-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Lists, 1971-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - "The Story of Christmas" (1968), Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - "Talk Out!" (1973), Archival Resource Key (Box 19)
    - Correspondence, 1972-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Interview with Douglas Davis, 1972 December; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound cassette Includes transcript (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Interview with Jane Davis, circa 1972; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound cassette Includes transcript (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Interview with Russ Connor, circa 1972; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound cassette Includes transcript (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Photographs from Broadcast, circa 1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Press Releases and Douglas Davis Catalog and CV, 1972-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - "Studies in Black and White Videotape #3", 1972; Archival Resource Key; 1 Videoreels (1/2 inch) (Box 19, Folder 26, Item 1)
    - "Studies in Color Videotape II", 1972; Archival Resource Key; 1 Videoreels (1/2 inch) (Box 19, Folder 26, Item 2)
  - "The Troubles: An Artist's Document of Ulster" (1972-1973), Archival Resource Key (Box 19)
    - General File, 1972-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - Interview with Les Levine, 1972; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound cassette (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Press Release and Clippings, 1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - "Towers" (1970), Archival Resource Key (Box 19)
    - Clippings, 1969-1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - Guide to Exhibition and its Installation, circa 1970; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound tape reel (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - Photographs, circa 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - Press Releases, Flyers, and Lists, 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - "Twentieth Century Italian Art from the Carlo F. Bilotti Collection" (1967), Archival Resource Key (Box 19)
    - Catalog Drafts, circa 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 34)
    - Clippings, 1966-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 35)
    - Correspondence, 1966-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 36)
    - Lists, circa 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - "Twentieth Century Italian Art from the Carlo F. Bilotti Collection" (1967), Archival Resource Key (Box 20)
    - Photographs of Artwork, circa 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Photographs of Artwork, circa 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Photographs of Installation, 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Press Release, Catalog, and Announcement, 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - "Twice as Natural: 19th Century American Genre Painting" (1973-1974), Archival Resource Key (Box 20)
    - Bills, 1973-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Catalog, 1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Clippings, 1973-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1973-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1973-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1973-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1973-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Insurance, 1973-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Loan Dispersal, 1973-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Loan Forms and Receipts, 1973-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Loan Forms and Receipts, 1973-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Loan Forms and Receipts, 1973-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - "Twice as Natural: 19th Century American Genre Painting" (1973-1974), Archival Resource Key (Box 21)
    - Notes, circa 1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - "Two Aspects of an Illusion" (1971-1972), Archival Resource Key (Box 21)
    - Catalog Drafts and Final Catalog, circa 1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Catalog Copyright Registration, 1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Clippings, Press Release, and Announcement, 1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 4)
      Oversized clipping and poster in OV 25
    - Correspondence and Résumés, 1971-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Insurance, 1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Interview with Michael Mazur, circa 1971; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound tape reel Includes transcript; 1 Sound cassette Includes transcript (Box 21, Folder 7)
      Sound tape reel contains part 1 of interview, and sound cassette contains part 2.
    - Interview with Paul Gedeohn, circa 1971; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound cassette Includes transcript (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Photographs, circa 1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - "Women in the Arts Festival" (1972), Archival Resource Key (Box 21)
    - Artist Information, circa 1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 10)
      Oversized poster in OV 25
    - Clippings, 1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1971-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Lists, circa 1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Loan Forms, Receipts, and Insurance, 1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Press Releases, Announcements, and Flyers, circa 1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Oversized "American Art Deco Architecture" Photographs digitized with box 6, folder 27, circa 1974-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Oversized "Art Deco" Material digitized with box 6, folders 30 and 35, 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Oversized "Art from Finland" Clipping digitized with box 8, folder 3, 1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Oversized "Destruction Art" Material digitized with box 13, folders 2, 14, and 16, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Oversized "Documentation" Material digitized with box 13, folders 20 and 31, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Oversized "The Dominant Woman" Material digitized with box 13, folders 33, 35, 37, and 51, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Oversized "Energy Sculpture" Clippings digitized with box 14, folder 4, 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Oversized "Forms in Metal" Material digitized with box 14, folders 34 and 35, 1974-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Oversized "Hans Richter Retrospective" Sketch digitized with box 15, folder 15, circa 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Oversized "Jacques Kaplan's Private Collection" Clipping digitized with box 15, folder 49, 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Oversized "N-Dimensional Space" Photographs digitized with box 16, folder 40, 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Oversized "Posters by Artists" Poster digitized with box 17, folder 13, circa 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Oversized "Projected Art" Poster digitized with box 17, folder 45, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Oversized "Rene Bouche: Portraits of Figures in the Arts" Material digitized with box 18, folders 37 and 44, 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Oversized "Schemata 7" Pamphlet digitized with box 18, folder 51, 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Oversized "Art Deco" Clippings digitized with box 7, folder 31, 1970-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box OV 23, Folder 8)
  - Oversized "Art Deco" Clippings digitized with box 7, folder 45, 1970-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box OV 23, Folder 9)
  - Oversized "Art in Jewelry" Clippings digitized with box 8, folder 20, 1965-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box OV 23, Folder 10)
  - Oversized "Art in Jewelry" Clippings digitized with box 8, folder 42, 1965-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box OV 23, Folder 11)
  - Oversized "Art in Process: The Visual Development of a Collage" Posters digitized with box 9, folder 44, 1964-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box OV 23, Folder 12)
  - Oversized "The Dominant Woman" Posters digitized with box 13, folder 53, circa 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box OV 23, Folder 13)
  - Oversized "Art in Process: The Visual Development of a Collage" Posters digitized with box 9, folders 43, 54, and 64, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box OV 24)
  - Oversized "Art in Process IV" Galleys digitized with box 10, folder 9, 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box OV 24)
  - Oversized "Art in Series" Clippings digitized with box 10, folder 28, 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box OV 24)
  - Oversized "Art Nouveau" Photographs digitized with box 10, folder 57, circa 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box OV 24)
  - Oversized "Artists Select" Material digitized with box 10, folder 61 and box 11, folders 7 and 50, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box OV 24)
  - Oversized Douglas Davis Installation Notes digitized with box 11, folder 58, circa 1971; Archival Resource Key (Box OV 24)
  - Oversized "Artists Videotape Performances" Magazine digitized with box 11, folder 63, 1971; Archival Resource Key (Box OV 24)
  - Oversized "Destruction Art" Clippings digitized with box 13, folders 3 and 4, 1966, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box OV 24)
  - Oversized "Les Formes Vivantes: Alexander Archipenko" Catalog Draft digitized with box 14, folder 21, 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box OV 25)
  - Oversized "Italian Visual Poetry" List digitized with box 15, folder 37, circa 1973; Archival Resource Key (Box OV 25)
  - Oversized "Jacques Kaplan's Private Collection" Galleys digitized with box 15, folder 43, circa 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box OV 25)
  - Oversized "N-Dimensional Space" Material digitized with box 16, folders 29 and 31, 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box OV 25)
  - Oversized "Projected Art: Artists at Work" Material digitized with box 18, folder 8 and 14, 1968-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box OV 25)
  - Oversized "Two Aspects of an Illusion" Material digitized with box 21, folder 4, 1971; Archival Resource Key (Box OV 25)
  - Oversized "Women in the Arts Festival" Poster digitized with box 21, folder 10, 1972; Archival Resource Key (Box OV 25)